- I didn't invent them. They're there.
- In what universe?
(Sheldon:)In all of them, that is the point.
(Penny:)Do you guys mind if I start?
(Penny:)- Penny.
- Yeah?
(Sheldon:)That's where I sit.
(Penny:)So sit next to me.
- No, I sit there.
- What's the difference?
- Here we go.
In winter, that seat is close enough
to the radiator to remain warm...
(Sheldon:)...yet not so close
as to cause perspiration.
In the summer, it's in a cross breeze created
by opening windows there and there.
(Sheldon:)It faces the television at an angle that is
neither direct, discouraging conversation...
(Sheldon:)...nor so far wide
as to create a parallax distortion.
(Sheldon:)I could go on,
but I think I've made my point.
(Penny:)Do you want me to move?
(Penny:)- Well...
- Just sit somewhere else.
(Sheldon:)Fine.